Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/

Top Skills

Sales Management
B2B Sales
Business Development

Languages

Russian Lithuanian English

Mckinley Bergstein

Account Manager at PVcase

Austria

Summary

Experienced Account Executive with a demonstrated history of working in the marketing and advertising industry. Skilled in Communication, Account Management, Direct Sales, and Business Development. Strong sales professional with a Bachelor's degree focused in International relations from London Metropolitan University.

Experience

awsm. agency
Advisor for Business Development
August 2023 - Present (6 months)
Lithuania

PVcase

Account Manager
January 2023 - Present (1 year 1 month)
Lithuania

Favro

Senior Account Executive March 2022 - December 2022 (10 months) Sweden

Managing two SDR's to build a pipeline for the SaaS vertical. Everything from prospecting to closing deals: identifying personas, companies, building sequences, reviewing contracts, presenting the product and eventually closing the deal.

Whatagraph

2 years

Senior Client Partner
October 2021 - February 2022 (5 months)
Netherlands

OKRs for 2021:

- Expanding market share in the Baltic region with cold outreach.
- Knowledge share sessions: invite external sales professionals to learn about best practices.
- Taking part in the hiring progress. Help evaluate the fit of us and the applicant for each other.

Client Partner

February 2021 - October 2021 (9 months)

Netherlands

You were probably expecting some fancy buzzwords here, so here's what matters:

- Q1 % 109 of target
- Q2 % 103 of target
- Q3 % 121 of target

Partner Development Team Lead

March 2020 - February 2021 (1 year)

Netherlands

Whatagraph is the fastest growing startup in Lithuania.

Not just a catchy phrase: Outbound team grew fourfold in the period of 3 months, going from under %10 of net new monthly revenue to almost %40.

Girteka Logistics

Sales Manager

August 2019 - March 2020 (8 months)

Vilnius, Lithuania

Establish business relations with potential company clients in the Scandinavian market

Provide high level of customer service

Ensure high sale and quality KPIs on a weekly basis

Maintain and update sales and customer records

Work in cooperation with colleagues to ensure on-time delivery by planning and schedulling routes

Delivery organization and documents administration

ARKET

1 year 9 months

Store Controller

January 2019 - July 2019 (7 months)

London, United Kingdom

- Ensure compliance on store accounting, payroll and cash handling policies and procedures
- Complete and ensure all cash office and safety routines regarding money handling
- Train and inform store personnel on administrative policies

Extra Sales Responsible October 2018 - January 2019 (4 months) London, United Kingdom

Sales Associate November 2017 - October 2018 (1 year) London, United Kingdom

Church's
Sales Associate
December 2016 - November 2017 (1 year)
London, United Kingdom

Education

London Metropolitan University

Bachelor's degree, International relations · (2016 - 2019)